(Sheldon:)Yes, amusing.
(Sheldon:)Extraordinary intelligence might well
appear extraterrestrial to you...
(Sheldon:)...but let me be more specific.
(Sheldon:)I believe you know why I'm here
in the laundry room.
(Penny:)Better acoustics
for your throat singing?
[VOCALIZING]
(Sheldon(trying it):)It's actually not bad.
(Sheldon(trying it):)But my true purpose in being here
will be revealed...
(Sheldon(trying it):)...in this brief PowerPoint presentation.
Ahem. Lights.
"Why Sheldon Cooper, PhD...
(Sheldon(trying it):)...should go to Switzerland
to see the CERN Super Collider:
(Sheldon(trying it):)A PowerPoint presentation
by Sheldon Cooper, PhD."
(Leonard:)Oh, for God's sakes.
(Sheldon:)Here, we have a highly gifted researcher
in the field of particle physics...